[{"answer": "Charlize Theron.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "How do you actually pronounce your name?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "Charlize Theron.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "What is the correct South African, dare I say it, African way of pronouncing this?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "And you quite consciously went and taught yourself how to speak in an American accent, right?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Every day.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "Do you speak African certainly?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Can you speak African to her?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Oh, I think more fluently than I speak English.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "So you speak it completely fluently?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "Woody?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "None of this -- there's no truth to it whatsoever.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "Guilty as charged?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "But he calls you Chuck?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Because I want to actually work until I'm 108 and I don't think you can't have longevity if you just kind of fall back on one aspect of what you are.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "Heading that way?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think human beings are -- I think we're pretty complicated.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "There's never the safe one, is there?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "Yes, we got plenty of time, seriously.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Oh, dear God, what is this, an hour show?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "So far, I said.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Do you really love the aging process?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Look, I'm only 35.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Is that because it's obviously treating you quite well?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "I -- the first thing I do is I inspect every closet and drawer.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "So you get to these random houses, and what do you do?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "There are guys going to say who is this weirdo?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "I've gotten a lot better.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "It's fascinating watching you because I know you don't like watching yourself, do you?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "God, no.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "Do you know how much money you've taken at the box office in movies you've been in?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "That sounds good.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "That's not bad, is it?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "I care.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "You don't care how much they make, these films?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "HERON: I guess I would take the one that makes the billion dollars, but the critics don't care for it because then I can go make seven of the ones that I love.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Which one would you prefer at this stage of your career?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "I'm sorry.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Hey, Todd, do we even have factory work?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "That was the greatest gift I think I've ever been given in my career.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "I mean, when you look back on it now, obviously brilliant for you in your career -- but to actually play that role, what was the experience like?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Yes, look, it's absolutely amazing to win an Academy Award.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "I did, yes.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Did you watch the Oscars as a young girl?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "ORGAN: Have you met him?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "The first time I met him, I had just won the Academy Award.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "When did you meet him?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "The nicest things that any icon or hero could possibly say to you, things that I'm so not deserving of.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "And what did he say to you?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Just, you know, giving me credit for being a South African and kind of putting South Africa on the map, which I didn't, but I'll take that any day from Nelson Mandela.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Any other?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Women?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "I don't know if they were women but I know another category South Africans have won.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Who else?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Look, I don't know.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "How much of it is down to what happened, if anything?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "I think it is a lack of education.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "What is the main reason do you think that it is so bad in South Africa, and what can be done to tackle it properly do you think?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "You can go to our Web site, Charlizeafricaoutreach.org, and you can buy them there.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "How do you get them?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Yes, directly -- look, here is the thing.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "And directly help?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "It is knowledge.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "What is the single biggest problem that the young in South Africa just don't really want to use condoms or even know much about them, is that the problem?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "Well, I loved Tatiana's book and, you know, this is a story that is particularly relevant to me.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "What was it about the story here which grabbed your attention?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "It really ranks with me strongly because the subject matter is so personal.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "But where does this rank for you personally?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "I think Kristin Scott Thomas, you know, who I first worked with on \"The English Patient\" is, you know, one of the smartest, best actresses.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "What was the thinking?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "Movie opens next Friday.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "And Harvey, when does the film get released here in America?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "I never did, but as a liberal.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "I mean, did you ever meet Margaret Thatcher?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "She put her principles first.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "And that I think is often the greatest characteristic of any leader, isn't it?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "I'm going to be run out of all my social circles, Piers.", "docId": "110716pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "How are your liberal friends going to react, Harvey, when you seem to be the one man who rehabilitates the Thatcher image for the world?", "qSentId": 645}]